(Leonard:)I thought you weren't interested in me.
(Lesley:)That was before I saw you handling that
beautiful piece of wood between your legs.
(Leonard:)You mean my cello.
(Lesley:)No, I mean the obvious,
crude double entendre.
(Lesley:)I'm seducing you.
(Leonard:)No kidding.
What can I say?
I'm a passionate and impulsive woman.
(Lesley:)So how about it?
(Leonard:)Gee...
- Is it the waitress?
- Penny? What about her?
(Lesley:)I saw your pupils dilate
when you looked at her...
(Lesley:)...which, unless you're a heroin addict,
points to sexual attraction.
I did have a poppy-seed bagel
for breakfast...
(Leonard:)...which could give
a positive urine test for opiates...
(Leonard:)...but certainly not dilate my pupils...
...so I guess there was no point
in bringing it up.
- You and the waitress, then.
- No, no.
(Leonard:)There's nothing going on
between Penny and me.
(Lesley:)So you're open to a sexual relationship?
(Leonard:)Yeah. Yeah, I guess I am.